Guide to the William T. Grant Foundation records FA004
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 1940-1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; 3; Tavistock Institute of Human Relations; Spock, Benjamin (1903-1998); Freud, Anna (1895-1982); Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic; Goodall, Jane (1934); 96.9 Cubic Feet 246 letter document boxes, 5 legal document boxes, 4 half-legal boxes, 1 card f
  - Grant files, 1940s - 1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; A
    - Center of child Psychoprevention and Child Psychotherapy - Reports, Publications - Joseph P. Tenns, M.D. (69-0165-66), 1967 (Box 36, Folder 470-472)
    - University of Chicago - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Diana T. Slaughter, Ph.D. (74-0579-74), 1977-1983 (Box 37, Folder 473-476)
    - University of Chicago Family Study Center - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Nelson N. Foote, B.S. (0053), 1953-1956 (Box 37, Folder 477)
    - Child Development Center - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Peter B. Newbauer, M.D. (67-0125-61), 1970-1972 (Box 37, Folder 478-479)
    - Child Study Association of America - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (67-0032-49), 1947-1962 (Box 37, Folder 480-483)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Administration - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1976-1989 (Box 38, Folder 484)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Applications - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1979 (Box 38, Folder 485)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Finance - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1979-1981 (Box 38, Folder 486)
    - Child Trends Inc. - General Correspondence - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 487)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Report, Final - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1981-1983 (Box 38, Folder 488)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Report, Progress - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1980 (Box 38, Folder 489)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Report, Progress - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 490-492)
    - Child Trends Inc. - Nicholas Zill, Ph.D. (0685), 1979 (Box 38, Folder 493)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1973-1980 (Box 38, Folder 494)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Applications - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1978-1997 (Box 38, Folder 495-496)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Bibliography - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1976-1983 (Box 38, Folder 497)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Finance - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1974-1982 (Box 39, Folder 498)
    - Children's Defense Fund - General Correspondence - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1979-1983 (Box 39, Folder 499)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Report, Final - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 500)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Reports, Progress - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1975-1980 (Box 39, Folder 501)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1974-1982 (Box 39, Folder 502-507)
    - Children's Defense Fund - Marian Wright Edelman (79-0455-73), 1973-1981 (Box 39, Folder 508)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center Adolescent Unit - Bibliography - J. Roswell Gallagher, M.D. (69-0070-54), after 1950 (Box 40, Folder 509)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center Adolescent Unit - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - J. Roswell Gallagher, M.D. (69-0070-54), 1949-1968 (Box 40, Folder 510-520)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Administration - T. Benny Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1972-1981 (Box 40, Folder 521)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Applications - T. Benny Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1972-1978 (Box 40, Folder 522-523)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Bibliography - T. Benny Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 524)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Finance - T. Benny Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1974-1983 (Box 40, Folder 525)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Report, Final - T. Benny Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1982 (Box 40, Folder 526)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Reports, Progress - T. Berry Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1973-1977 (Box 41, Folder 527-528)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - T. Berry Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 529-532)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - T. Berry Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1974-1979 (Box 42, Folder 533-535)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Child Development Unit - T. Berry Brazelton, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1972-1978 (Box 42, Folder 536)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Administration - Dorothy B. Villee, M.D. (78-0376-72), 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 537)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Application - Dorothy B. Villee, M.D. (0608), 1976 (Box 42, Folder 538)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Finance - Dorothy B. Villee, M.D. (0608), 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 539)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Reports, Final - Dorothy B. Villee, M.D. (0608), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 540)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Reports, Progress - Dorothy B. Villee, M.D. (0608), 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 541)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Dorothy B. Villee, M.D. (0608), 1976 (Box 42, Folder 542)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Administration - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), 1978-1981 (Box 42, Folder 543)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Applications - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), 1978-1982 (Box 42, Folder 544)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Finance - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 545)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Reports, Final - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), 1981 (Box 43, Folder 546)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Reports, Progress - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 547)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), after 1978 (Box 43, Folder 548)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center - Peter H. Wolff, M.D. (78-0663-78), 1978 (Box 43, Folder 549)
    - Children's Hospital at Buffalo - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Thomas F. Anders, M.D. (81-0276-70), 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 550-552)
    - Children's Hospital of the District of Columbia - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Ann P. Barnet, M.D. (75-0427-73), 1975 (Box 43, Folder 553)
    - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Report, Final - Marie C. McCormick, M.D., ScD.; Geoge J. Peckham, M.D. (86-1095-86), 1992 March 31 (Box 43, Folder 554)
    - Children's Hospital at Stanford - Administration - Gregory K. Fritz, M.D. (81-0758-81), 1981-1984 (Box 43, Folder 555)
    - Children's Hospital at Stanford - Application - Gregory K. Fritz, M.D. (81-0758-81), 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 556)
    - Children's Hospital at Stanford - Bibliography - Gregory K. Fritz, M.D. (81-0758-81), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 557)
    - Children's Hospital at Stanford - Finance - Gregory K. Fritz, M.D. (81-0758-81), 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 558)
    - Children's Hospital at Stanford - Report, Final - Gregory K. Fritz, M.D. (81-0758-81), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 559)
    - Children's Hospital at Stanford - Gregory K. Fritz, M.D. (81-0758-81), 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 560)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center of Northern California - Administration - Herbert A. Schreier, M.D. (80-0745-80), 1980-1982 (Box 43, Folder 561)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center of Northern California - Application - Herbert A. Schreier, M.D. (80-0745-80), 1980-1982 (Box 43, Folder 562)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center of Northern California - Finance - Herbert A. Schreier, M.D. (80-0745-80), 1980 (Box 44, Folder 563)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center of Northern California - Reports, Final - (80-0745-80), 1983 (Box 44, Folder 564)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center of Northern California (80-0745-80), 1971-1980 (Box 44, Folder 565)
    - Children's Rehabilitation Institue - John F. Kennedy Institute - Reports, Publicatons/Manuscripts - Paula Tallal, Ph.D. (74-0524-74), 1971-1980 (Box 44, Folder 566-567)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Administration - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1974-1978 (Box 44, Folder 568)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Applications - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 569)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Bibliography - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), after 1977 (Box 44, Folder 570)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Finance - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1975-1979 (Box 44, Folder 571)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - General Correspondence - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1974-1977 (Box 44, Folder 572)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Reports, Progress - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1976-1979 (Box 44, Folder 573)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 574-575)
    - Citizen's Committee for Children of New York - Bernard C. Fisher (74-0260-70), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 576)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 577)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1978 (Box 44, Folder 578)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 579)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Administration - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1973-1977 (Box 44, Folder 580)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Applications - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 581)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Finance - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1977-1980 (Box 44, Folder 582)
    - National Council of Organizations for Children and Youth - Report, Final - Bernard C. Fisher (0633), 1980-1982 (Box 44, Folder 583)
    - Clark University - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Seymour Wapner, Ph.D. (74-0575-74), 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 584-586)
    - Cleveland Metropolitan General Hospital - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Laille Gabinet, Ph.D. (unassigned grant number), 1975 (Box 45, Folder 587)
    - University Hospitals of Cleveland - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - L. Douglas Lenkoski, M.D. (unknown grant number), 1970-1975 (Box 45, Folder 588-589)
    - University of Colorado - Reports, Final - C. Henry Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70), 1985 (Box 45, Folder 590)
    - University of Colorado - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - C. Henry Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70), 1977-1985 (Box 45, Folder 591-593)
    - University of Colorado - Administration - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70A), 1974-1988 (Box 46, Folder 594)
    - University of Colorado - Applications - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70A), 1970-1978 (Box 46, Folder 595)
    - University of Colorado - Bibliography - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70A), 1976 (Box 46, Folder 596)
    - University of Colorado - Finance - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70A), 1975-1979 (Box 46, Folder 597)
    - University of Colorado - Reports - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70A), 1972-1980 (Box 46, Folder 598)
    - University of Colorado - Administration - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70B), 1973-1989 (Box 46, Folder 599)
    - University of Colorado - Applications - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70B), 1973-1988 (Box 46, Folder 600)
    - University of Colorado - Finance - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70B), 1975-1985 (Box 46, Folder 601)
    - University of Colorado - General Correspondence - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70B), 1978-1985 (Box 46, Folder 602)
    - University of Colorado - Reports, Progress - C. Henry Kempe, M.D.; Ruth Kempe, M.D. (83-0304-70B), 1974-1988 (Box 46, Folder 603)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Administration - William K. Frankenburg, M.D. (83-0714-80), 1980, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 604)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Applications - William K. Frankenburg, M.D. (83-0714-80), 1980-1983 (Box 47, Folder 605)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Bibliography - William K. Frankenburg, M.D. (83-0714-80), after 1985 (Box 47, Folder 606)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Finance - William K. Frankenburg, M.D. (83-0714-80), 1981-1985 (Box 47, Folder 607)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Reports, Final - William K. Frankenburg, M.D. (83-0714-80), 1980-1983 (Box 47, Folder 608-609)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - William K. Frankenburg, M.D. (83-0714-80), 1980, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 610)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Administration - Katherine Tennes, M.A. (81-0757-81), 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 611)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Applications - Katherine Tennes, M.A. (81-0757-81), 1980-1982 (Box 47, Folder 612)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Finance - Katherine Tennes, M.A. (81-0757-81), 1982-1985 (Box 47, Folder 613)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Report, Final - Katherine Tennes, M.A. (81-0757-81), 1982-1985 (Box 47, Folder 614)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Katherine Tennes, M.A. (81-0757-81), 1986 (Box 47, Folder 615)
    - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center - Katherine Tennes, M.A. (81-0757-81), 1980-1983 (Box 47, Folder 616)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Administration - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1978-1984 (Box 48, Folder 617)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Applications - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1975-1985 (Box 48, Folder 618)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Bibliography - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1975-1978 (Box 48, Folder 619)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Finance - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1977-1985 (Box 48, Folder 620)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Report, Final - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1978-1985 (Box 48, Folder 621-622)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1978-1983 (Box 48, Folder 623-624)
    - University of Colorado Institute for Behavioral Genetics - Robert J. Plomin, Ph.D.; John C. DeFries, Ph.D. (84-0598-75), 1974-1984 (Box 48, Folder 625)
    - Columbia University - Publications - Thomas G. Bever, Ph.D. (75-0580-75), 1976 (Box 48, Folder 626)
    - Columbia University - Publications - Thomas G. Bever, Ph.D. (72-0379-72), 1976 (Box 48, Folder 627)
    - Columbia University of Physicians and Surgeons - Administration - Michael Katz, M.D. (72-0379-72), 1978-1985 (Box 48, Folder 628)
    - Columbia University of Physicians and Surgeons - Applications - Michael Katz, M.D. (82-0688-79), 1978-1981 (Box 48, Folder 629)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians - Finance - Michael Katz, M.D. (82-0688-79), 1984-1987 (Box 49, Folder 630)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians - Progress, Reports - Michael Katz, M.D. (82-0688-79), 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 631)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians - Final Program Report - Michael Katz, M.D. (82-0688-79), 1987 (Box 49, Folder 632)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Michael Katz, M.D. (82-0688-79), 1978-1982 (Box 49, Folder 633)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Site Visits - Michael Katz, M.D. (82-0688-79), 1978-1982 (Box 49, Folder 634)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Administration - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D. (82-0688-79), 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 635)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Application - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D. (79-0689-79), 1979-1986 (Box 49, Folder 636)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Bibliography - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D. (79-0689-79), after 1986 (Box 49, Folder 637)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Report, Final - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D. (79-0686-79), 1981 (Box 49, Folder 638)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D. (79-0686-79), 1980-1986 (Box 49, Folder 639)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Publications/Manuscripts - C. Dominique Toran-Allenrand, M.D. (79-0686-79), 1980 (Box 49, Folder 640)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Publications - Eric R. Kandel, M.D. (74-0527-74), 1976 (Box 49, Folder 641)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons - Publications - Myron Winick, M.D. (72-0381-72), 1975-1978 (Box 49, Folder 642)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Administration - Jack Elinson, Ph.D. (80-0717-80), 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 643)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Application - Jack Elinson, Ph.D. (80-0717-80), 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 644)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Finance - Jack Elinson, Ph.D. (80-0717-80), 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 635)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Report, Final - Jack Elinson, Ph.D. (80-0717-80), 1982 (Box 49, Folder 636)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Administration - Ann Brunswick, Ph.D. (79-0687-79), 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 637)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Application - Ann Brunswick, Ph.D. (79-0687-79), 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 638)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Publications - Ann Brunswick, Ph.D. (79-0687-79), 1979-1989 (Box 50, Folder 639-640)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Reports - Ann Brunswick, Ph.D. (79-0687-79), 1981-1989 (Box 50, Folder 641)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Ann Brunswick, Ph.D. (79-0687-79), 1979 (Box 50, Folder 642)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Publications - Viola W. Bernard, M.D. (68-0088-56), 1959-1964 (Box 50, Folder 643-646)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health - Final Report - Steven Schinke, Ph.D. (84-0953-84), 1988 (Box 50, Folder 647)
    - Columbia University School of Public Health School of Social Work - Publications - Steven Schinke, Ph.D. (84-0953-84), 1985-1988 (Box 50, Folder 648-649)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Publications - Steven Schinke, Ph.D. (84-0953-84), 1985 (Box 51, Folder 650-651)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Administration - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1971-1980 (Box 51, Folder 652)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Applications - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1980-1987 (Box 51, Folder 653)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Bibliography - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1986 (Box 51, Folder 654)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Finance - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1982 (Box 51, Folder 655)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Report, Final - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1988 (Box 51, Folder 656)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Reports, Progress - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1981-1983 (Box 51, Folder 657)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work - Sheila Kamerman, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (80-0731-80), 1980-1983 (Box 51, Folder 658)
    - Community Research Associates - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Bradley Buell (69-0010-45), 1948-1968 (Box 52, Folder 659-669)
    - Community Research Associates - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Bradley Buell (69-0010-45), 1946-1981 (Box 53, Folder 670-673)
    - University of Connecticut - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Evelyn B. Thoman, Ph.D. (82-0386-71), 1957-1979 (Box 53, Folder 674-677)
    - University of Connecticut - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Evelyn B. Thoman, Ph.D. (82-0386-71), 1971-1982 (Box 54, Folder 678-683)
    - University of Connecticut - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Benson E. Ginsburg (72-0385-72), 1973-1978 (Box 54, Folder 684-686)
    - University of Connecticut - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Benson E. Ginsburg (72-0385-72), 1975-1978 (Box 55, Folder 687-694)
    - Cornell University - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Sayles & Strauss (50-0048-50), 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder 695)
    - Cornell University - Administration - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1981-1984 (Box 55, Folder 696)
    - Cornell University - Applications - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1981 (Box 55, Folder 697)
    - Cornell University - Bibliography - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1986 (Box 55, Folder 698)
    - Cornell University - Bibliography - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 699)
    - Cornell University - Bibliography - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1981-1988 (Box 55, Folder 700)
    - Cornell University - Reports, Final/Publications - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1983-1986 (Box 55, Folder 701-702)
    - Cornell University - Reports, Interim - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1981-1985 (Box 55, Folder 703)
    - Cornell University - Reports, Interim - Urie Bronfenbrenner, Ph.D. (82-0797-00), 1981 (Box 55, Folder 704)
    - Cornell University Medical College N.Y. Hospital - Administration - Daniel M. Stern, M.D. (81-0754-81) (82-0754-01: ODF Supplement), 1981-1989 (Box 56, Folder 705)
    - Cornell University Medical College N.Y. Hospital - Applications - Daniel M. Stern, M.D. (81-0754-81) (82-0754-01: ODF Supplement), 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 706)
    - Cornell University Medical College N.Y. Hospital - Finance - Daniel M. Stern, M.D. (81-0754-81) (82-0754-01: ODF Supplement), 1981-1988 (Box 56, Folder 707)
    - Cornell University Medical College N.Y. Hospital - Daniel M. Stern, M.D. (81-0754-81) (82-0754-01: ODF Supplement), 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 708)
    - CUNY: City University of New York - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Sylvia Brady, Ph.D. (71-0175-67), 1968-1982 (Box 56, Folder 709-710)
    - CUNY: Hunter College - Administration - Lisa Kuhmerker, Ph.D. (81-0771-81), 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 711)
    - CUNY: Hunter College - Applications - Lisa Kuhmerker, Ph.D. (81-0771-81), 1981 (Box 56, Folder 712)
    - CUNY: Hunter College - Finance - Lisa Kuhmerker, Ph.D. (81-0771-81), 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 713)
    - CUNY: Hunter College - General Correspondence - Lisa Kuhmerker, Ph.D. (81-0771-81), 1981 (Box 56, Folder 714)
    - CUNY: Hunter College - Final Report - Lisa Kuhmerker, Ph.D. (81-0771-81), 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 715)
    - CUNY: The Research Foundation - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Mary Engel, Ph.D. (71-0339-71), 1974 (Box 56, Folder 716)
    - University of Denver - Administration - Marshall M. Haith, Ph.D. (79-0392-75), 1975-1981 (Box 56, Folder 717)
    - University of Denver - Application - Marshall M. Haith, Ph.D. (79-0392-75), 1974-1976 (Box 56, Folder 718)